So you're just about to reach the end of
你的学习进度已经快接近
the first week of material on the first course in this specialization.
这个专项课程的第一门课的第一周的末尾了
Let me give you a quick sense of what you'll learn in the next few weeks as well.
让我给你快速地介绍一下 下一周我们将要学习什么内容
As I said in the first video,
在第一个视频里我已经说过
this specialization comprises five courses.
这个专项课程一共有五门课
And right now, we're in the first of
目前我们在它的第一门课
these five courses which teach you the most important foundations,
在这门课中将教会你最重要的基础知识
really the most important building blocks of deep learning.
它们真的是深度学习最重要的基石
So by the end of this first course,
当你学到第一门课的结尾
you know how to build and get to work a deep neural network.
你将知道如何建立一个深度神经网络并且使它奏效
So here the details of what is in this first course.
下面是一些有关第一门课的细节
This course is four weeks of material.
这门课有四个星期的材料
And you're just coming up to the end of
目前你就要完成第一周的学习了
the first week when you saw an introduction to deep learning.
当你看到了深度学习的介绍后
At the end of each week,
在每一周的结尾
there are also be 10 multiple-choice questions that
也都会有十个多选题
you can use to double check your understanding of the material.
你可以用来检验自己对材料的理解
So when you're done watching this video,
所以当你看完这个视频的时候
I hope you're going to take a look at those questions.
我希望你能看看这些问题
In the second week, you then learn about the Basics of Neural Network Programming.
在第二周 你会学习一些有关神经网络的编程知识
You'll learn the structure of what we
了解神经网络的结构
call the forward propagation and the back propagation
我们把它叫做正向传播和反向传播
steps of the algorithm and how to implement neural networks efficiently.
逐步的完善你的算法 以及如何使得你的神经网络高效实现
Starting from the second week,
从第二周开始
you also get to do a programming exercise
你也会开始做一些编程训练（付费项目）
that lets you practice the material you've just learned,
这让你练习你刚刚学到的材料
implement the algorithms yourself and see it work for yourself.
自己实现算法 并看到它为自己工作
I find it really satisfying when I learn about algorithm and they
当我学习算法的时候 我发现它真的很令人满意
get it coded up and I see it worked for myself.
把它编写出来 让它为我自己工作
So I hope you enjoy that too.
所以我希望你们也喜欢
Having learned the framework for neural network programming in the third week,
在第三周学习了神经网络编程的框架后
you code up a single hidden layer neural network. All right.
你将可以编写一个隐藏层神经网络
So you learn about all the key concepts needed
所以你需要学习所有必需的关键概念
to implement and get to work in neural network.
来实现神经网络的工作
And then finally in week four,
最后在第四周
you build a deep neural network and neural network with
你建立了一个深层的神经网络
many layers and see it worked for yourself.
它有许多层 并且你能看到它为你工作
So, congratulations on finishing the videos after this one.
所以 恭喜你完成了这段视频
I hope that you now have a good high-level sense of what's happening in deep learning.
我希望你现在对深度学习的情况有一个更高层次的理解
And perhaps some of you are also assigned to,
也许你们中的一些人也有一些想法
has some ideas of where you might want to apply deep learning yourself.
可能想要有你自己应用深度学习的地方
So, I hope that after this video,
我希望在这段视频结束之后
you go on to take a look at the 10 multiple choice questions that follow this video
我们来看看这10个选择题
on the course website and just use
它们会被显示在课程网站上
the 10 multiple choice questions to check your understanding.
将会有10个选择题来检查你的理解
And don't review, you don't get all the answers right the first time,
不用去复习前面的知识 有的答案你现在是不知道的
you can try again and again until you get them all right.
你可以一次又一次地尝试 直到你把它们都做好
I found them useful to make sure that I'm understanding all the concepts,
我发现它们很有用 以确保我理解所有的概念
I hope you're that way too.
我希望你也可以做到
So with that, congrats again for getting up to
我的话说完了 再次祝贺你
here and I look forward to seeing you in the week two videos.
我期待在本周的另外两个视频中见到你